http://www.columbusfoundation.org/privacy-policy

LOG IN TO MANAGE YOUR GIVING
STUDENTS:
Log in to your Scholarship Application.
LOGIN
Register
or
Forgot Username?
or
Forgot Your Password?
Register
or
Forgot Username?
or
Forgot Your Password?
Skip to Content
Privacy Policy
This website is owned and operated by The Columbus Foundation. We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity, and security of personal information entrusted to us. Your right to privacy is very important to us. We recognize that providing The Columbus Foundation with your personal information is an act of trust. The following Privacy Policy was developed to assure you that we take seriously our responsibility to protect customer information, and use it only in ways that are consistent with your wishes.
Our Policy
At our site we don’t collect personally identifiable information about individuals unless they knowingly provide it to us. So, if you just want to browse and learn about our services, programs, and benefits, we invite you to do so. As a casual, unregistered visitor to our site we’ll recognize your home server, but not your e-mail address or any other personal or system information.
If you are a Columbus Foundation donor and want to access information about your fund, it will be necessary for you to provide personally identifiable information. This may include your name, address, email address, and phone number. Any information you provide is downloaded from the web server and maintained in a secure system. Changes to your information online may only occur after you have logged in with a registered user name and password.
Our Customer Lists
When you register to receive information, such as an e-Newsletter, or identify your areas of interest, we add your name to our customer list. Once you provide us with personal or professional information, that data remains confidential and will only be used by The Columbus Foundation. We will not share any information you provide to us with any other organization. We will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes.
Communication From Us
We use our customer lists for follow-up contacts with you. This is our way of keeping you up to date on our services, programs, and benefits. This also enables you to receive current information about the local, national, and global community to better meet your philanthropic needs. We maintain e-mail mailboxes in an effort to support customers who visit us online. We read every e-mail message that we receive and do our best to respond within 48 hours, if a response is required. We do not record your e-mail address unless you have voluntarily provided it to us when you register to receive follow-up information or an e-newsletter. If you do provide us with your e-mail address, and register your interest in receiving follow-up information, we may notify you from time to time about Columbus Foundation products, services, and benefits. At all times, we include “opt-out” instructions with the e-mail that is sent to you. You can update or delete your account information and preferences or “opt-out” at any time.
Cookies
We use “cookies” (small pieces of information stored on your computer) on certain parts of our website. The cookies allow us to track your session, particularly when you access your donor account. We do not use cookies to collect any type of personal information or to extract any information from your computer.
Security Online
When using our forms to register or receive information from The Columbus Foundation, we use secure pages to ensure that the information sent between your computer and our system is secure. We use the Secure Service Layer (SSL) encryption method for all secure submissions. This method is generally accepted to insure that the transmission of personal information is secure. Some common browsers, i.e. Internet Explorer, make it obvious when information is being passed in a secure manner by displaying either a completed key or a closed lock on the screen.
Copyright and Trademark Notice
Copyright of the text contained in this website is owned by The Columbus Foundation. All rights are reserved. All text, images, graphics, and other materials on this website are subject to the copyrights and other intellectual property rights of The Columbus Foundation and its affiliated companies. These materials may not be copied, reproduced, or distributed for commercial purposes, nor may these materials be modified, or uploaded, downloaded or reposted, in whole or in part to other websites. All graphic designs and visual/audio content included on this site, such as photographs, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, and software, is the property of The Columbus Foundation and is protected by U.S. patent and copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all software material on this site is the exclusive property of The Columbus Foundation or its software suppliers and is protected by U.S. copyright and patent laws. The content and software on this site may be used as a resource only. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display, or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited. The names, trademarks, logos, designs, and trade dress shown on this site are owned by The Columbus Foundation and are protected by the trademark laws of the U.S. and other jurisdictions. Any use of “The Columbus Foundation,” its logo, or text, or graphic materials contained in this website in any manner to express or imply endorsement, sponsorship, affiliation, or association of the user with or by The Columbus Foundation, is strictly prohibited unless permission has been granted. Nonprofit organizations that are the recipient of a Columbus Foundation grant should contact the Foundation for information about publicizing grants and use of the logo.
Web Links to This Site
You may establish a hypertext link to this site from your website, so long as the page containing the link properly attributes the linked site to The Columbus Foundation and does not state or imply any sponsorship of your site by The Columbus Foundation. Without prior written consent of The Columbus Foundation, you may not create a link to this site that incorporates or relies upon, in whole or in part, any content from any page on this website, or that incorporates any copyrighted or otherwise intellectual property of The Columbus Foundation.
Links to Other Sites
As a service to you, The Columbus Foundation provides links to websites of various philanthropic and nonprofit organizations. A link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization, sponsorship, or affiliation with respect to such site, its owners, or providers. When leaving www.columbusfoundation.org, we recommend you check the privacy policy of the site you are visiting before providing personal information.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to update and change the Policy as needed.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact Brad Britton, Director of Planned Giving and General Counsel at 614/251-4000 or by e-mail.
SIGN UP FOR FOUNDATION UPDATES
First Name
This field is required.
Last Name
This field is required.
Email Address
This field is required.
Submit
Thank you for signing up!
SIGN UP FOR FOUNDATION UPDATES
First Name
This field is required.
Last Name
This field is required.
Email Address
This field is required.
Submit
